Bang!
I'm here!
Where am I?
Here! Here! Here!
Come here!
Where is it? Here.
We're at Trampopid!
Good morning!
I'm here for the barbecue.
Oh! Nice!
That's great!
I'm Karen!
I'm Mel!
Hine!
Where are you?
I'm here to do backflips!
Backflips?
Why?
I told the staff in my dream.
You'll never do it.
So I asked him five times.
I said, "Sure.
I was wondering if you'd let me do it.
I think my dream might come true today.
Let's make our dreams come true!
Let's make it come true!
Let's do it!
I'm looking forward to it!
Wow!
It's crooked!
Look! Look!
It's amazing! It's flying!
Wow!
Oh, my God!
We're gonna do it now!
Can you do it?
I'm gonna do it!
Yeah!
I'm in the hanging flower!
That's great!
Today, I'm going to challenge you.
We can't do it alone.
That means we need a teacher or something.
I'll call a teacher.
Are you there?
I'm Mr. Aizawa!
I'm Daihei Aizawa!
My homeroom teacher at middle school.
Nice name.
I'm Mr. Watanabe, your teacher!
You said one more?
I'm Watanabe!
It's been a while!
Today, three of you want to try Bakudan or Chugaiwa.
Can you do it?
Yes, if you give me 6 years.
I won't go back to school.
In fact, we all dance.
They're more athletic than most.
That's the assumption.
If all I had to do was do a middle/outer loop on a trampoline or something...
I can do it today.
Surprisingly, it's a plan.
Surprising plan!
Because it would be awesome to do it on stage.
That's cool.
Maybe we can make our dreams come true.
Let's go for it today!
Let's go!
[fast forward]
[explosions]
Trying on three people.
Please wait a moment.
You're not stiff, are you?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It doesn't hurt that much?
They'll know.
Oh, my God!
Look.
The soles of Mr. Watanabe's socks.
They're trampoline shoes.
I'm going to ask everyone to wear them.
Don't turn your legs this way!
Trying on with three people
You know, when we do this in the lesson
only Pearl and Miyu are awake.
Please lean your body forward.
I'm leaning forward
Ouch!
It's OK.
Okay, let's go.
Let's cross.
Yes, sir.
Yay!
Tonight's photo was taken after the get.
Three, two, one.
I'm going to confront Mr. Kanazawa of ЗаLing to see what kind of monster he is!What kind of monster will be facing off against Mr. Kanazawa of ЗаLing!
[Drone]
Oh!
This is the back pen.
Can you guys get this ready today?
Can you do it?
The biggest obstacle to getting a back pen is...
Fear of flying backwards.
So I'd like to help you learn a little bit about this fear of flying backwards.
I'd like to work on this fear of jumping backwards a little bit at a time.
Please do.
I'm going to start with something simple.
The backward rollback.
Oh!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not gonna let you do it.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's hard to tell.
Okay, let's do it one at a time.
Here we go.
I got it! I got it!
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Okay, okay.
Here we go.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Beautiful.
Rime-chan is great!
Let's go!
Go for it!
Come on.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
I'm ready for my active adventure.
Active?
What adventure?
No way.
My body's always been small.
Keep looking at your knees.
I'm gonna push you.
I'm gonna give you one last push with my hand.
Come on.
Keep looking at your knees and push with your hand
Oh, that's hard.
Come on.
Push with your hand
Push with your hand.
Here we go.
Oh, wow.
That's it.
I got it.
Yeah!
Isn't this fun?
With the spinning.
It's safe either way.
Let's fly with this.
You have one and two, right?
One, two.
It's going down.
He's going down.
Straighten up and fall down.
Please do that much
I'm going to fall over
Now that's what I'm talking about, the one with the bent buttocks.
It was falling over, so I'm going to fall over while looking at it
1,2
Fall over
That's good.
Here we go.
One, two.
It's good.
Here we go.
1,2
That's good.
That's the first time I've ever been complimented on how good it is.
It's the first time I got a compliment.
You did a good job on the cut.
I gave him a compliment and it was like half a job.
Really?
The plan is to grab the hand.
You have to practice grabbing hands.
We used to do gymnastics in pairs.
Back to back.
Like this.
Let's try this.
Bend over at the waist until you put your hands on the floor.
Put your hands on your hips.
Hands on your hips.
Hands on the floor.
Bend over at the waist.
When I put my hands on you, bend over.
Please.
That's it.
You're so beautiful.
Oh, my God.
Your legs are so beautiful.
That's great.Excellent.
I have to practice to get my hands on it.
You can push here head first.
One, two.
Ehhhh.
Awesome.
Three.
Coming up.
One, two.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,1 7,18,19,20,21,22,23,24,25,26,27,28,29,30 ,31,32,33,34,35,36,37,38,39,40,40,41,42, 42,43,44, 44,44,44,44,45,46,47,48,49,49,5 0,51,52,52,53,54,55,56,56,57,58,59,59,59,60,60,61,62,62,63,63,64,64,65,66,67,67,67, 68,68,69,70,71,72, 74,72,73,74,74,74,75,7 6,78,79,79,80,10,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,18,20
1,2,3
Yo-ho!
OH!
OK.
You got it.
Now, with assistance, the back pen is ready.
It's done.
Wow.
Yay!
Yeah!
zzzz!
Gummy.
Still going on.
I love it.
Yeah, it's right here.
Right here.
It's a big stock.
Big.
It's out.
Light blue.
Hey. Hey.
You okay?
You're gonna take it off Belly's foot.
You okay? You okay?
You okay, Jajaylo?
You all right, Jajaylo?
Youth.
Come on!
Now that was a jump! It was a zero!
It was a zero on the jump!
It was right above! And it was pretty much spot-on from there!
That's it!
Ready, one, two, three!
Oh!
Let's bridge!
Bridge!
One, two, three.
Oh!
That's it! Like that!
I'll do my best!
It's hard.
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Very difficult!
Bend your knees too much!
Too much knee bend!
Yes!
Whoa! Whoa!
Knees bent, sir.
Huh.
That's great.
Knees bent, sir.
That's good.
So, well, that was a pretty good time.
Ew.
Yay.
Oh, man.
Last one?
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's do the last one.
Uh, wait.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
Ah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Let's go one more time.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
I could jump, but I thought my hand was gonna close.
I thought my hand was gonna close.
Uh-oh.
Wow.
Punch.
There you go.
Oh, oh, oh, I knew that jump was good.
But your hands are stuck and your body is spinning.
More like this.
Just look at it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I don't know, but I'm getting better at it.
That's great!
But I think I'm doing the best I've ever done.
Maybe the best I've ever done on my own.
Thank you!
Hands, right? Just a little jump.
My hand's still there.
My hand's stopped.
Oh, my God, it's flying right up.What, it's flying right above us.
Oh! Oh! Kill kill kill kill!
Yeah!
Just so you can do it without me.
I'd love to have you do it without me.
I can't go home now, can I? I'm not making my dream come true?
You know what? It's just...
I wanted to say good-bye.
We'll continue with the second part.
We'll continue with the second part until you're done, okay?
Yes! I'll do it! I'll do it!
Let's make it happen!
Thank you!
Thank you for watching the video!
Will there be a next one? Enjoy!
Please give us a high rating!
Bye bye!
Subscribe to our channel!